dennys.com 2018-10-13

# Privacy Policy - Denny's

USA Canada

### Denny's Privacy Policy Highlights — US

At Denny's. we understand the value of your privacy. This Policy is designed to help you understand what information Denny's collects about you, when Denny's collects such information, and what we do with that information. Please see the sections below addressing Information We Collect and How We Use Your Information. This page provides a general overview of each topic, but feel free to follow the link at the bottom of each section for more detailed information. If you have any questions or feedback regarding Denny's Privacy Policy, please contact us through the web form on the websites Contact Us page.

#### Scope of Policy

This Policy applies to customer information Denny's Inc. (Denny's) collects in the United States at Denny's restaurants (restaurants), through our website, and through our mobile applications. As a global company, Denny's has a separate privacy policies in place for each country. Please visit the webpage for your country for privacy policy information.

Read our entire US privacy policy.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

Denny's collects information from you that you provide to us while using our services, including:

  * Information you provide us when we request personal information, such as in job inquiries with Denny's, franchise inquires, gift certificate purchases, customer feedback, contest entry, subscription to informational email service, and requests for information about Denny's.
  * Information you give us, such as during transactions, surveys, website registrations, and mobile applications.
  * Information from other sources, such as companies that help us to update our records, and
  * Information automatically collected when you visit or use our websites, such as via cookies and device information, and in stores, such as via video cameras.

Read more about Information Denny's May Collect About You

#### How Do We Use Your Information?

Denny's does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties, but we may use your information internally to support our business functions or share and receive information with our franchisees to support our franchise network. For example, your information may be used in service fulfillment, internal business processes, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. We may combine all the information we collect from different sources.

Under the following limiting circumstances, we may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * with service providers or suppliers that help with our business operations or joint products.
  * with your consent.
  * when necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Denny's, its customers, or its associates, or
  * when otherwise required by law.

Read more about How We May Disclose Your Information Outside Denny's

### Privacy Policy — Full Policy — US

#### Notice and Scope of Our Privacy Practices

This policy addresses how and why we collect your personal information, how your information is protected, and when and with whom we share your information. Our goal is to provide clear, prominent, and easily accessible information about our privacy practices. 

This Policy applies to customer information we collect in the United States at Denny's restaurants, through our websites, and through our mobile applications. As an international company, Denny's has separate privacy policies in place for each country in which we are located. Personal information about our customers may be processed and stored in the United States or any other country in which Denny's or our service providers maintain facilities. However, Denny's requires each member of our corporate family and our service providers to protect your information, regardless of where it is store, in accordance with local laws and our policies.

#### Information Denny's May Collect About You

##### 1\. Information You Provide to Us

While visiting the Denny's site you may be asked to provide information that personally identifies you (name, address, billing address, email address, home telephone number, mobile telephone number, credit card number and social security number). The following are sample areas in the Denny's site where we request personal information:

  * Job Inquires with Denny's, Inc.
  * Franchise Inquiry
  * Gift Certificate Purchase
  * Customer Feedback
  * Contest Entry
  * Subscription to Informational E-mail service
  * Request Information about Denny's

The personal information that we collect varies depending on the activity you wish to conduct on the web. We will need more information for job inquiries, franchise inquiries, gift certificate purchase, contest entry and real estate site submission than we require for customer feedback, information request and e-mail subscriptions.

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, birth date and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. If you have not opted out of receiving marketing materials, we may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new Denny's services and special offers we think you'll find valuable.

You can choose not to allow us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes by indicating your preference at the time of collection or by responding to the promotional e-mail in the manner provided. In certain circumstances, consent may be sought after the information has been collected but before use (for example, when we want to use information for a purpose not previously identified).

##### 2\. Mobile Applications & Other Automatically Generated Information

We receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our websites, emails, online advertising, and mobile device applications. Our purpose is to allow the websites and applications to work correctly, to evaluate their use, and to support website analytics and marketing campaigns. Some examples include:

  * We may collect technical information such as your internet protocol address, your device operating system and browser type.
  * We use "cookies" to recognize you as you use or return to our sites. A cookie is a small text file that a website or email may save to your browser and store on your hard drive.
  * We may also use web beacons. Beacons allow us to know if a certain page was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our website and other sites were effective.

Our mobile applications collect certain information automatically, including:

  * the type of mobile device you use and your mobile operating system, unique device identifiers (UDID), and the IP address of your mobile device
  * information about the way you use the applications, and
  * information about the location of your device, such as when you search for or check in at a restaurant.

You must first provide permission through your device before our mobile applications obtain such location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity. Denny's and our service providers may use and store this information, in combination with other location-based information such as IP address and billing or postal code provided by you at time of your mobile application registration, to provide enhanced location based services, such as restaurant locations. If you would like to opt-out of providing your precise location information, you may do so by uninstalling the application or adjusting the permissions on your mobile device.

##### 3\. Information from Third Party Vendors

We may receive personal information about you from other sources as well. Examples of these sources are entities that can help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, and help prevent or detect fraud.

#### How We May Disclose Your Information Outside Denny's

Denny's does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties, but we may disclose your information internally to support our business functions or with our franchisees to support our franchise network.We only disclose your personal information to third parties with your prior consent or under the following limited circumstances.

##### 1\. Customer Comments and Complaints.

If you submit comments through the web site, we may use or post your comments (or a portion or variation of your comments), along with your first name, city or town on this web site or other media without payment or compensation to you. In instances when we receive customer complaints or feedback concerning specific franchised restaurants, we will forward the feedback to the franchised restaurant owner.

##### 2\. Service Providers.

We may disclose or otherwise make available personal information about you to service providers that help with our business operations. Examples are marketing and online advertising vendors, billing and refund vendors, payment card processors, and companies that help us improve business and our websites. We may also work with analytics companies to help us understand how our mobile applications are being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. Your personal information may be stored and processed by our service providers in the United States or other locations where the service providers or Denny's maintain facilities. We require our service providers to keep your information secure. In addition, our service providers may not use or disclose personal information for any purpose other than providing the services on our behalf.

##### 3\. Legal Requirements and Protection of Our Company.

We may disclose your information in situations when the sharing is necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Denny's, our customers, our associates, or any other person, or where otherwise required by law. Examples include protecting the health or safety of customers, or addressing crimes committed on Denny's property. Data from in-store security cameras may also be provided to law enforcement upon written request. Denny's may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by applicable law. We may also need to disclose personal information to enforce our policies or agreements including the collection of amounts owed to us or to protect users of our website(s)and apps. from fraudulent or abusive use.

##### 4\. Sales, Mergers, and Other Business Combinations.

We also reserve the right to disclose or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger or any other type of acquisition, disposal or financing of all or any portion of Denny's, Inc., DFO, LLC, or Denny's Corporation.

#### Your Consent and Changes to Policy

By using our website and submitting the personal information requested, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner described in this policy by Denny's.

From time to time, with your consent, we may disclose information with carefully selected companies who may offer you products and services of interest. You can choose not to allow us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes by indicating your preference at the time of collection or by responding to the promotional e-mail in the manner provided.

Denny's reserves the right to change its policy in this regard at any time in the future. In the event Denny's does make a material change to its policy, a notification of such change will be posted on the website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose.

#### How we secure your information

We have implemented security measures we consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online or through our services, and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. In the unfortunate event that your "personally identifiable information" (as the term or similar terms are defined by any applicable law requiring notice upon a security breach) is compromised, we may notify you by e-mail (at our sole and absolute discretion) to the last e-mail address you have provided us in the most expedient time reasonable under the circumstances; provided, however, delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation. From time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.

#### Children Under the Age of 13

While we are happy to have you visit the Denny's web site with your children, the Denny's site is a general audience site and is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Please contact us via the Contact Us section of this policy if you believe we may have collected information from your child and we will work to delete it.

#### Links to Other Sites

We may provide links to third party sites on our web site. We are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those other sites. The privacy policy of other sites will differ from Denny's privacy policy. Please read the privacy policy of any third party web site before providing any personal information.

#### Contact Us

Contact us through our web form on the websites Contact Us page for questions about Denny's Privacy Policy or any other general feedback or questions.

#### Notice to California Residents: 

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by Denny's to third parties for the third parties direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this privacy policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an email to: [http://www.myDenny's.net/gct/guestcall.nsf/CallRecord?OpenForm ](http://www.mydennys.net/gct/guestcall.nsf/CallRecord?OpenForm)

### Denny's Privacy Policy Highlights — Canada

At Denny's. we understand the value of your privacy. This Policy is designed to help you understand what information Denny's collects about you, when Denny's collects such information, and what we do with that information. Please see the sections below addressing Information We Collect, How We Use Your Information, and How to Access Your Information or Contact our Privacy Officer. This page provides a general overview of each topic, but feel free to follow the link at the bottom of each section for more detailed information.

#### Scope of Policy

This Policy applies to customer information Denny's Inc. (Denny's) collects in Canada at Denny's restaurants (restaurants), through our website, and through our mobile applications. As a global company, Denny's has a separate privacy policies in place for each country. Please visit the webpage for your country for privacy policy information.

Read our entire Canada privacy policy.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

Denny's collects information from you that you provide to us while using our services, including:

  * Information you provide us when we request personal information, such as in job inquiries with Denny's, franchise inquires, gift certificate purchases, customer feedback, contest entry, subscription to informational email service, and requests for information about Denny's.
  * Information you give us, such as during transactions, surveys, website registrations, and mobile applications.
  * Information from other sources, such as companies that help us to update our records, and
  * Information automatically collected when you visit or use our websites, such as via cookies and device information.

Read more about Information Denny's May Collect About You

#### How Do We Use Your Information?

Denny's does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties, but we may use your information internally to support our business functions or share and receive information with our franchisees to support our franchise network. For example, your information may be used in service fulfillment, internal business processes, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. We may combine all the information we collect from different sources.

Under the following limiting circumstances, we may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * with service providers or suppliers that help with our business operations or joint products.
  * with your consent.
  * when necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Denny's, its customers, or its associates, or 
  * when otherwise required by law.

Read more about How We May Disclose Your Information Outside Denny's

#### How to Access Your Information or Contact Our Privacy Officer

If you would like more information about Denny's privacy policies, to review the personal information that Denny's has on file for you, or to file a complaint, please contact our Privacy Officer:

[http://www.myDenny's.net/gct/guestcall.nsf/CallRecord?OpenForm](http://www.mydennys.net/gct/guestcall.nsf/CallRecord?OpenForm) or by mail to the Privacy Officer at Denny's, Inc., P-8-6, 203 East Main Street, Spartanburg, SC, USA, 29319

### Privacy Policy — Full Policy — Canada

#### Notice and Scope of Our Privacy Practices

This policy addresses how and why we collect your personal information, how your information is protected, and when and with whom we share your information. Our goal is to provide clear, prominent, and easily accessible information about our privacy practices. 

This Policy applies to customer information we collect in Canada at Denny's restaurants, through our websites, and through our mobile applications. As an international company, Denny's has separate privacy policies in place for each country in which we are located. Personal information about our customers may be processed and stored in the United States or any other country in which Denny's or our service providers maintain facilities. However, Denny's requires each member of our corporate family and our service providers to protect your information, regardless of where it is store, in accordance with local laws and our policies.

#### Information Denny's May Collect About You

##### 1\. Information You Provide to Us

While visiting the Denny's site you may be asked to provide information that personally identifies you (name, address, billing address, email address, home telephone number, mobile telephone number, credit card number and social security number). The following are sample areas in the Denny's site where we request personal information: 

  * Job Inquires with Denny's, Inc. 
  * Franchise Inquiry 
  * Gift Certificate Purchase 
  * Customer Feedback 
  * Contest Entry 
  * Subscription to Informational E-mail service 
  * Request Information about Denny's 

The personal information that we collect varies depending on the activity you wish to conduct on the web. We will need more information for job inquiries, franchise inquiries, gift certificate purchase, contest entry and real estate site submission than we require for customer feedback, information request and e-mail subscriptions. 

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, birth date and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. If you have not opted out of receiving marketing materials, we may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the website, new Denny's services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. 

You can choose not to allow us to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes by indicating your preference at the time of collection or by responding to the promotional e-mail in the manner provided. In certain circumstances, consent may be sought after the information has been collected but before use (for example, when we want to use information for a purpose not previously identified). 

##### 2\. Mobile Applications & Other Automatically Generated Information

We receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our websites, emails, online advertising, and mobile device applications. Our purpose is to allow the websites and applications to work correctly, to evaluate their use, and to support website analytics and marketing campaigns. Some examples include:

  * We may collect technical information such as your internet protocol address, your device operating system and browser type.
  * We use "cookies" to recognize you as you use or return to our sites. A cookie is a small text file that a website or email may save to your browser and store on your hard drive.
  * We may also use web beacons. Beacons allow us to know if a certain page was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our website and other sites were effective.

Our mobile applications collect certain information automatically, including: 

  * the type of mobile device you use and your mobile operating system, unique device identifiers (UDID), and the IP address of your mobile device
  * information about the way you use the applications, and
  * information about the location of your device, such as when you search for or check in at a restaurant. 

You must first provide permission through your device before our mobile applications obtain such location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity. Denny's and our service providers may use and store this information, in combination with other location-based information such as IP address and billing or postal code provided by you at time of your mobile application registration, to provide enhanced location based services, such as restaurant locations. If you would like to opt-out of providing your precise location information, you may do so by uninstalling the application or adjusting the permissions on your mobile device.

##### 3\. Information from Third Party Vendors

We may receive personal information about you from other sources as well. Examples of these sources are entities that can help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, and help prevent or detect fraud.

#### How We May Disclose Your Information Outside Denny's

Denny's does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties, but we may disclose your information internally to support our business functions or with our franchisees to support our franchise network.We only disclose your personal information to third parties with your prior consent or under the following limited circumstances.

##### 1\. Customer Comments and Complaints.

If you submit comments through the web site, we may use or post your comments (or a portion or variation of your comments), along with your first name, city or town on this web site or other media without payment or compensation to you. In instances when we receive customer complaints or feedback concerning specific franchised restaurants, we will forward the feedback to the franchised restaurant owner.

##### 2\. Service Providers.

We may disclose or otherwise make available personal information about you to service providers that help with our business operations. Examples are marketing and online advertising vendors, billing and refund vendors, payment card processors, and companies that help us improve business and our websites. We may also work with analytics companies to help us understand how our mobile applications are being used, such as the frequency and duration of usage. Your personal information may be stored and processed by our service providers in the United States or other locations where the service providers or Denny's maintain facilities. We require our service providers to keep your information secure. In addition, our service providers may not use or disclose personal information for any purpose other than providing the services on our behalf.

##### 3\. Legal Requirements and Protection of Our Company.

We may disclose your information in situations when the sharing is necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Denny's, our customers, our associates, or any other person, or where otherwise required by law. Examples include protecting the health or safety of customers, or addressing crimes committed on Denny's property. Data from in-store security cameras may also be provided to law enforcement upon written request. Denny's may provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by applicable law. We may also need to disclose personal information to enforce our policies or agreements including the collection of amounts owed to us or to protect users of our website(s)and apps. from fraudulent or abusive use.

##### 4\. Sales, Mergers, and Other Business Combinations.

We also reserve the right to disclose or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger or any other type of acquisition, disposal or financing of all or any portion of Denny's, Inc., DFO, LLC, or Denny's Corporation.

#### Your Consent 

Denny's will only collect, use, and disclose your personal information with your consent, except in a few narrow circumstances as provided by law, such as when your information is necessary for legal or security purposes. However, the form of consent may differ depending upon the circumstances and the type of information that is being collected. Under some circumstances, you may be explicitly asked for your consent through a written form, electronic agreement, or orally in person or through the telephone. When your information is collected for direct marketing purposes, your consent is implied unless you request that your information not be given to other organizations by checking the appropriate box on the materials provided to you. When we receive customer compliments, complaints or feedback concerning specific franchised restaurants, we will forward the feedback to the franchised restaurant owner. By submitting your comments to DFO, you consent to our sharing such information with the franchisee.

#### Changes to Our Policy

Denny's reserves the right to change its policy in this regard at any time in the future. In the event Denny's does make a material change to its policy, a notification of such change will be posted on the website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose.

#### How we secure your information

We have implemented physical, organizational, and technological security measures we consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against loss or theft or unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification of your personal information under our control. 

Denny's only retains your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws and for such longer reasonable time as may apply from time to time under our internal policies and procedures. 

#### Children Under the Age of 13

While we are happy to have you visit the Denny's web site with your children, the Denny's site is a general audience site and is not designed nor intended to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Please contact our Privacy Officer if you believe we may have collected information from your child and we will work to delete it. 

#### Links to Other Sites 

We may provide links to third party sites on our web site. We are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those other sites. The privacy policy of other sites will differ from Denny's privacy policy. Please read the privacy policy of any third party web site before providing any personal information.

#### Contact Us

Please feel free to contact our Privacy Officer with any questions or comments about this policy or about how your information is handled by email at [http://www.myDennys.net/gct/guestcall.nsf/CallRecord?OpenForm](http://www.mydennys.net/gct/guestcall.nsf/CallRecord?OpenForm) or by mail to the Privacy Officer at Denny's, Inc., P-8-6, 203 East Main Street, Spartanburg, SC, USA, 29319.

**Date Adopted: September, 2013**
